Cyril Alvarez Adriaansen

Cryptocurrency Specialist | Execution/Sales Trader Full-stack Javascript Developer | BlockChain Developer

+34 653 895 269 (



me@cyril.page



Cvril.page



<u>Cyril-al-adriaansen</u> in



SKILLS

Business Development
Cryptocurrency Specialist
BlockChain Development
Trade Positioning
Technical Analysis
Hedge Funds Strategies
Programming

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF OXFORD Fintech Program 2018

UNIVERSITY OF MONTREAL Bachelor of Political Science Candidate 2002 - 2004

CERTIFICATIONS

Chartered Institute for Securities & Investment (CISI)

IronHack, Full-stack JavaScript

Certified Bitcoin Professional (CBP)

Certified Blockchain Developer (CBD)

Certified Solidity Developer (CSD)

Certified Smart Contract Developer (CSCD)

PROFILE

Dynamic, accomplished Trading & Developer Professional highly regarded for 15+ years of progressive experience in driving equity and cryptocurrency trading/sales and blockchain efforts. Respected as a motivational, influential leader and collaborator who uses technical expertise to understand markets and trading positions, ensuring profitability. Out-of-the-box thinker committed to making continuous improvements in business development, risk management, and trading/market analysis to enable growth.

EXPERIENCE

HEAD OF TRADING & BLOCKCHAIN 2gether | Madrid | 2017 - Present

- Deliver critical strategic and tactical insights as a member of the Steering Committee.
- Provide crucial advice across the organization on Blockchain, Cryptocurrency, Fintech & Decentralised Finance (DeFi).
- Demonstrate exceptional technical acumen in designing the Trading & Blockchain architecture.
- Build pre-ICO and ICO Smart contracts in Solidity, ensuring attainment of short and long-term goals.
- Helmed initiative for the Initial Coin Offering (ICO), and authored a subsequent handbook to convey best practices and common issues during the effort.

CRYPTO CONSULTANT / DEVELOPER

Independent | Geneva, London, Madrid | 2013 - Present

- Incorporate data-driven assessments in investing in a wide array of cryptocurrencies, and act as an ICO Advisor.
- Expand expertise at every opportunity with all aspects of arbitrage and day trading
- Focus on improving forecasting and trend assessments.

SALES/EXECUTION TRADER, Managing Director

Castle Harbour Securities | Geneva, London, Bermuda | 2011 - 2013

- Exceeded annual commission quota by 15%, handling equity, bond, and forex trade execution via DMA, algorithms, dark pools, and brokers while collaborating with cross-functional employees.
- Advised/identified appropriate investments and managed capital exposure as a trusted expert with risk management principles; noted as essential to a 20% upturn in overall company growth.
- Handled extensive market information, research, and news to organize sales efforts and improve trading.
- Achieved optimal trade execution by forging productive, professional relationships with multiple stakeholders, excelling as the primary liaison with technical trading questions.
- Provided clients with a wide array of input to improve their portfolio and exceed expectations.

Cyril Alvarez Adriaansen

Cryptocurrency Specialist | Execution/Sales Trader Full-stack Javascript Developer | BlockChain Developer

+34 653 895 269 (



me@cyril.page



Cyril.page



Cyril-al-adriaansen in



VCard



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Linux

Github

Smart Contracts

Google App Script

Javascript (MERN)

Python

HTML & CSS

INTERESTS

Fintech
Artificial Intelligence

Solar Energy

Geopolitics

History

Traveling

Formula One

EXPERIENCE continued

SALES/EXECUTION TRADER, Vice President BTIG LTD. | London | 2009 - 2011

- Revised investment history and incorporated technical and fundamental analysis to establish trading positions.
- Analyzed strategic risk assessment strategies to maximize portfolio performance and minimize downside exposure consistently, building out subsequent standard operating procedures used across the entire organization.
- Drove strict and continuous regulatory compliance, and oversaw financial and technical analysis to determine lucrative trading situations, boosting profits by up to 10% despite volatile market conditions.
- Maintained comprehensives record of clients and fostered continued workflow
- Provided periodic feedback to clients and gained trust as a dedicated and capable resource.

TRADE SUPPORT, Associate

Jabre Capital | Geneva | 2007 - 2009.

- Supported 5 portfolio managers with \$4B under management in various funds; performed extensive research on new systems and technologies to improve market assessments and other data-heavy decisions.
- Maintained transactions in a wide array of systems, coordinating with a team of 30.
- Built tailored reports on convertible bonds, equity, options, and more while focusing on positive business impacts.
- Identified efficiency improvements to increase year-over-year profits.

Additional Experience: Trainee Derivatives Advisor, Bank Pictet & Cie, 2006

Languages: French, English, Spanish

REFERENCES

Salvador Casquero 2gether | Founder +34 687 88 08 22



Omar Ulrich Castle harbour | CEO +41 79 859 54 00



Gary Hayes BTIG LTD. | Former CEO +44 20 7663 1700



Daniel Horsley
Anavio Capital | Founder
+44 78 1844 4100

